Hello Hello Friends Namaskar
that today
I will talk to you about the
best product of a start-up,
if I talk about the back of which industry, the
best product of Family
Arab countries, then it will
not be an exaggeration that Family is not only the
best product of this style but of the entire industry, it is such a beautiful
wallpaper, its Family is less and it has the
maximum features, about which I will
talk to you in detail through this video today, before that I heartily welcome you all to
my YouTube channel Health Tips Gyan and
greet you
friends, Family Help
is a policy at the time of limit, whose entry fee is from 18 years to
50 years, a group from zero to 35, 36 to 45,
656 to 661 renewal which will be lifelong in this policy,
payment is made if the entry
fee is more than six, then in that case the company
flashes 80%, 20% the
customer has to pay himself,
in the next life I will tell you in great detail
about this policy
and the recovery line according to it,
not of any browser  It is
not printed, it is not written by anyone, what the
underwriter says about this policy,
I will talk to all the Pune pass statements and we will
give you information about it, let's
start quickly, the start product is known as Family
Health Problems of Life Children,
its product, the editor
idea is to balance this product, it was
launched in 2018, what are the special features,
how does it work, include about them, if
you are going to wash and clean it with this water then the
minimum front and what the company says is
1 lakh 2 lakh 3 lakh 400005 10025 but I would
like to tell you that one and two so that the
company does not sell the policy, it has only been
handed over to that at this
time when we
go for treatment
in any hospital, the first thing that is done is now the
room rent, so the company, for example, if you
give a policy of one lakh, then I will give you 2000 front, that is
2 lakh 2,000, but the
pornographic clips that we take are sold for three blocks,
so we will talk about 3245
Ten-fifteen-twenty has ROM Redmi Note 5 in 39,
four lakh units are ₹5000 and five
ten-fifteen-twenty minutes definitely single
standard muscle whatever that request is the
actual cost whatever we have behind 10,000
well whatever request is that company does it
properly
with bright vibrancy the hospital
administration will be considered in
prostration
how to the invisible room rent this means
that if you are a cheap object of worship and
that you have and you have ever taken
more than five thousand during the treatment,
fish has been clearly posted, then
your entire bill will be tabled in net rate
so here I would request you
that if you have a three amount policy then
you should never take more than 5 thousand. If you
go for setting zoom treatment then there is
surgeon's fee, anti-aging
effect is there, medical practitioner's fee is there,
consultant's fee is there and then the
extra oil is there.  Cable is not there, won the third ODI,
blood oxygen operation, changes, medicine
truck and apart from this, if we
talk about all the laps, left 4G, if we get any kind of
report done, we diagnose it, then
whatever it is, it is not made at one end, there is more
point in it, the
cutter treatment Kunwar,
that if you are talking to me about this, only this one and one unknown,
along with this, this emergency ambulance,
if I talk to you from both the points, A A
Family Help Shimla Policy Chandragrahan,
talk to you that in the entire policy there are 2 points
where the company has made a limit, has
imposed a limit, the first is the track
treatment, it has a question after 2 years,
in this the limit free, your three
letters start with 25000 for a week,
431005 for 40,000, 10 for 50 thousand, 15
thousand and 25,750 are taken if you do both
in a year, you will get this money for 3 minutes,
if you get a statement done from the company on both the tracks at the same time, in
which the company gives 3 lakh 35 thousand to
him and highest feedback  If it was 75 thousand then this
company will give you a
maximum of 50,000 in 21 years
if your time symbol is black or
tempered glass and the new one that goes around the
second point emergency ambulance
person in the meantime you would like
express tribune whether it is diesel engine
or someone can ask them in this if
you need an ambulance then
you pay ₹15 in front clearly in one go
half a spoon and nothing else matters that
32 strips 45 and 15 have any
pigmented 7 and a half to fifteen this to you
and after that your pair ambulance
that ambulance hermb he had a wash and there is
no run out till four lakhs, there is a cover above 5 lakhs on the
temple run and from time to time in one and a half year
if you feel that whatever
your policy is you need center of performance on commodo channel
and maximum together
after that now there is prince hospitalization that
test you should get in this before one week from any one region
For treatment, you have to get admitted to the hospital, if you do
n't have to go there, then
in that case, whatever bills you have to pay for the seven days before admission
or after admission, if you do
n't open a post, then
when will you get treatment in 6183 doses, we will do that,
I made Baker treatment, okay
treatment, if I do a bathroom procedure,
any exam
question, it got burnt and as soon as I go to the hospital,
if there is any
treatment given in the CD, then you can
take it in the morning and you get treatment for three, four, five hours
and after that,
after getting treatment, you are
discharged on the same day, in that, minor
surgery is done, dimple surgery,
stone surgery or you have any kind of
fracture, then all that is
covered uselessly, no matter how much you beat, the next week is the
class paper,
if for any reason you
are not in the hospital, now you cannot go to the hospital, then the
doctor will visit your home and
treat you for three days, but it
provides quality and can
translate that
if any intestine  I have
any other question and want to get frostbite,
please do it like kidney, liver, etc., for that
someone
will donate for the treatment, then the
cost of the surgery of the male is also borne by the company,
regret ten percent down, if 5 lakhs
are returned then 50,000 and if before that 10
lakhs or 1 lakhs update is done maximum, Witcher
Research Labs does
this, its mother cost of health
checkup WhatsApp backup means that you have
given the policy and in any way your policy has been
received, there was no claim in this year,
I call it MCB login, this is the leg, then
if you have not received any claim, then the
company gives you a benefit, it is
less than the help, 379 positive
benefits start, they were 70, we
will measure and four lakh 23 thousand rupees and five
number 10 lakhs from 15 years, then in 2008, it got up
to 25 lakhs, clear and good sarees
reached ₹70, she used to give ₹70 to family members
So this is the limit for the entire family. If you have become
one among yourselves, get a checkup done. Be completely
religious. Give clothes to your family. Many
congratulations. This is also a very good feature that
after the OnePlus 6, in the next year, the
group couple is given a new baby at their home.
Now, after the scheme, the
baby will be added to it for the first
year without any premium. But keep in mind
that the contract in this will be
added in the second year
and in the first year, it will be taken from the members of Parliament
and its pressure will be reduced up to a maximum of Rs. 50,000.
Then I have issued an Emergency
Domestic Medical Unit
Certificate. In this case, if the patient has to go to
another hospital for any
emergency reason for any appointment and the
temple has not been cured in the previous chapter and his condition is
not improving, in that case, to ensure another treatment, according to the
semester, we
can use whatever services you have. There
is an option in Compensation Travels that if the subject in the checkpoint pass was
outside and along with it, the office is yours.  He gets
admitted in the hospital, give him a number, one of his
family members had taken him back, the
company has
left him 210 while returning,
ok, 1015, 2025,
then the company gives him a balance of 500, 1000 for
his work in these or above, you are seeing this,
till the time of leaving section 384 is filed against the 9th class family, it is not on DJ
select1 city reproduction of motor
image means if any gentleman who is positive
and he goes to the home town feeder of Policy Hospital Aligarh, then for
his last journey, for the
last rites, if there is any
famous saying in the water, then you
can see ₹ 5 in the bank account
Next9 Investment in Proper
Network Hospital Below are two ways in which the company does
treatment, which is called networking
and Saffron Top is preferred leadership,
I have given a registered benefit company in
which the company is towards the benefit hospital,
what the company does is to help its customers
suffering from fog, what is it,
in every city there are two such
private hospitals  So if you
select the later option on that, then the company gives
1% of your policy, for example, 3 lakh or 5 lakh, through this 3000, this
5000 and maximum ₹5000, the company gives
its patient once in a year for the
benefit of getting treatment in a referred network hospital,
right, so this is not a big feature,
you will get an update back
of the next 9 recommendations from the news room, the
first point in the number one side
was that the room rent
is unlimited in number five, nor
can any cost be met, but here
if the customer has taken share information, then the customer will
get salary or commission, then the company will
save the cost, so how will these companies decide,
10 to 15 out of 345,
he has a Chakra policy at present
and Vasundhara is on 500, the number of days he will
stay in the hospital will be decided by the company
and he will get an update of admission and discharge,
he is doing it for two days -
For a pimple, a person
is discharged on that date i.e. he
stayed in the hospital for 10 days, then the bus stand should be 800
to 1000 multiplied by 1 and 10, but the company will calculate its
price by
6490. Next, we make that
along with cardamom offering, Ayurvedic
treatment in which there is a five step Ayurveda wave in America,
these days there is Siddha and A A
homeopathic A A
treatment, its cost starts from 1 lakh to
25,
give different limits at night, you can email for 1 minute
brother, what
makes you special is that the customer
is admitted in the hospital and his condition is
not improving
because in this the company on its own has
given a promise to the customer that if you want,
your complete report is available from the
doctor. Here the company's network of medical
facilities has decided on this match, whatever is
printed on it, the treatment is complete,
voice mail chances are the company's
doctor will call you himself and
support you.  We will do it and help you in testing.
Next lakh hot you give number
per second. Medical shop in Indore
stadium has covered next 9
then A 10 is reproduction treatment
and reflection treatment will be done. If any
family is having
problem in fertility from Chishti Ujjain, then
this treatment is given. Flip covers
infotainment but we cover it from the third year
and for this the minimum requirement is up
to ₹5 lakh. If the policy is covered then
37 is covered. Okay,
naturally on the other hand, committee restoration is our
very good point.
What is the feature of the company in this that in
case you have quality, its solution was ₹5
and that policy from serial,
Maa Kasam, if you zoomed your pin, then
in that case, after completion in the fifth house, the
company will give you five times five
tablespoon sorry ginger Ravana. Whatever has
not been done by you, Sameshwar
company restores the policy at
this time. Yes, one thing to be kept very
careful about is that if your
policy  5 lakh number five lakh is for your use,
any one person has a disease,
pimples for his tractor,
you have to tighten your limit, if it is used in this later injury, then your limit will be reduced, who can
zoom on corruption, in that case the
company will restore you hundred percent,
but you cannot use it
on that disease, for this you should
already understand the inside, someone is using it
and you
cannot use it on patients suffering from accidental disease, so this
is a bit technical, understand it carefully
friends, it is made natural by Additional Commissioner
for Road Traffic Jam. Once in a policy,
if during a year you were travelling by two wheeler as a
policy holder and any
kind of accident occurs, in that case
whatever the basic spoon is, the company increases it by 25 percent,
their shop two wheeler
road accident is fine, whoever goes to it, should
understand that even if the sum of 20 lakhs, then that
twenty five percent increase will go up to
125 and if someone had a sum of 25 lakhs, then the sum will go up to
257 percent.  Take it and increase your understanding. The announcement will be made soon,
but the companies have been given permits.
We will make the maximum fifth cycle. So keep in mind
that your polish will increase by 25 per cent. The
States of Baroda used to impose a maximum
fine. So, the patient who is being
treated should
also have a helmet. Vehicle papers. There are pimples.
This is only Mahindra. Please
take my blessings. NCB
No Claim Bonus. If you have
not given any of these creams,
in that case the company does Bolo side in your body every year.
First it likes clean cold water.
Second side it does temple sense. It likes a
little attendance. It likes pocket.
You 210 till you have double, then the
company AB ES adds boil in your policy.
But if you
enjoy doing any business without you, then
give its limit. This is your first big success.
2.5 percent bonus will be returned - it will also be taken into account.
Question - it will be taken. In this way, it will
also be added and will be reduced.
Wherever there is darkness, it means that it
Benefits lot table juice destructive society
and at that time the benefit will not come
that this is the complete detail, notes about
information lollipop indicate and complete the
treatment before doing more positive
wedding document you get this, then for that
first shift exclusive wedding,
but still despite this
if something is sold or something is left
then you can also do some upkeep, you can see,
I will try to give you some good information from my side
about the best policy of the country's biggest company, health insurance
Plutarch, I have also taken the services of the superintendent for the last 15 years
and this product has been
running from B star Hans Pade One but we have been
crying in the time bad comments and
even today with the best product,
now talk about its cost, very cheap price,
anyone can easily buy it at such a price,
so
I have shared so much information with you, I
hope that all of you will also find the
information useful, if you are
going to take health insurance brother or any
minute venture friend is working then all of you  Keep
following our channel,
keep creating your information through Hadiths and knowledge
and if you like any kind of
information then share it with us,
subscribe to our channel
and if you find
our
things good then tell us by commenting and if you find
something bad or something that is not right, please
tell us that too so that we can improve it in the future
and
help us in giving you the best information.
Thank you very much for using us.